# JORGE HERNANDEZ

### CLOUD PRACTITIONER

# CONTACT

+1 951 379 8533

Moreno Valley, CA

in www.linkedin.com/in/jorgekwu

#### PROFILE

Hello, World. I was an assistant English professor and teacher in South Korea for 9 years. About a year ago, I decided that I wanted to drastically change my career and work on a team providing viable solutions to customers and business clients.

### EDUCATION

MA TESOL Azusa Pacific University 2011 - 2013

BA ENGLISH UC Riverside 2004 - 2008

### SKILLS

**Google Analytics** 

**Customer Service** 

WordPress

Facebook Business Suite

HTML 5/CSS

Visual Studio Code

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Web and Social Media Curator, Customer Service

https://patiofurnitureplus.com

Patio Furniture Plus, Ontario | Oct 2020 - Present

- · Created company website
- Manage Google Analytics/Adwords
- Curate social media: Instagram @patiofurnitureplus, Facebook Business Suite
- Provide customers with products and information
- Generate sales by answering customer questions
- Answer phones and help customers

#### **Assistant Professor**

Kwangwoon University, *Seoul, Korea* | 2015 - 2020 English language instruction ranging from conversational skills to business communication at the university level.

- Achieved high student evaluation: 4.89/5
- Strong reputation of valuable courses
- One semester of online instruction
- Provided students with feedback

## CERTIFICATION

AWS Cloud Practitioner | May 2021